Jesse O. Jones

+1 757-560-1203 • jesseoj98@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/jesseoj98 • github.com/jesseoj98

Full-stack software engineer with over 2 years of experience with Angular, Spring Boot, & MySQL technologies in the financial technology industry. Dedicated professional with a proven track record of delivery, communication, and efficiency. Strong computer science fundamentals from a comprehensive emphasis Bachelor of Science degree in Computer Science from the University of Wisconsin-Whitewater.

CAREER EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer I

June 2022 – December 2022

Fidelity National Information Services, Inc.

Milwaukee, WI

- Re-use oriented software engineering work on a large-scale Angular & Spring Boot application
- Main work done on enhancements to existing components as well as creating new components built off of existing infrastructure and fixing defects
- Lead delivery of a complicated debit feature, specifying the merge order of stories and providing knowledge transfer sessions on difficult technologies

Technologist Engineer I (FIS University Program)

June 2020 – June 2022

Fidelity National Information Services, Inc.

Milwaukee, WI

- Apart of an accelerated program to develop and grow the latest and most passionate fin-tech talent with on-the-job opportunities and training in a fast-paced industry
- Worked alongside three other FIS developers to program an Angular and Spring Boot application using a system of internal debit APIs
- Developed a batch processing sub-module application that is able to read, cross-check, and insert data off to submission to internal teams

TECHNICAL SKILLS

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

Fluent: Java, HTML, CSS, TypeScript, SQL

Familiar: C++, C#, C

TECHNOLOGIES

Angular NgRx Spring Boot
NodeJS Git ELK Stack

EDUCATION

University of Wisconsin-Whitewater

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science, Comprehensive Emphasis 3.779 Cumulative GPA, Magna Cum Laude Graduation Honors UWW Dean's List¹ (Fall 2016 – Spring 2020)

REFERENCES

Brina WhittierPrashant JoshiProject Manager IIBusiness Systems ManagerFISFISbrinawhittier@gmail.comprashant.desk@gmail.com

+1 414-379-9744 +91 990-101-3591

Hema Madadha

Release Train Engineer Director, Software Development

Chris Jones

FIS

FIS

hemamadadha@gmail.com chris.w.jones.ok@gmail.com

+1 773-412-9079 +1 405-640-8302

¹An honor given to those with a 3.4 GPA or higher in a single semester.